Guide to the Albert Ellis papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Audio Visual Material, 1953-2007
  - Subseries V.1: Audio cassettes, 1966-2007
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (RACHO and RACBA, she nds his lv and approval, he damng himself fr vacillatg, 1972 November 8; cont//she upsetg herself abt him; his vascillation)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (Therapist's Group, Nasheen, 1974 June 19; Michael cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (Therapist's Group, No. 2, 1972 November 29)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (NODLI, deprsd-pills-ex-alc-nd fr lv, 1972 November 14; AHCDA, Prog w/complsns and idea he can do, 1973 August 17)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (Therapists Group, 1972 December)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (GUHPE, fr of flure, shithd, tough on others, how to use rt, 1972 IRPLA, academic anx and foolishness of rating self, 1972 November 13)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (IHCSH, deprsn inability to choose a career, 1973 March; lv and ego-becmg less vulnerable tho in lv, 1973 March)
      (Note in case: IHCSH 1973 March-client's voice does not come through clearly, tape is therefore unsatisfactory for distribution. Bad. Avoid. J. Block)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (Autism, tlkg too much-perfectionism, 1973 February1; LEGBA, psychotic obsesd w/own and others failings, 1973 February 26)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (New ways in RET, 1972 June; wed group, 1974 September)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (Univ of Akron Workshop, Ellis, 1972 May 1; Univ of Akron Workshop cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (IASRP Workshop #2, Cleveland, Albert Ellis, James Bard, Edwin Wagner, Harold Fisher, 1971 May 2; cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (IASRP Instit. Adv. Study in Rat Psychotherapy Workshop, #1, Albert Ellis, Jim Jones, Al Canty, Chuck Baty, 1971 March 9; cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (Albert Ellis, RET Workshop Cleveland, 1973 May 19; RET Dem. Young black male, angry at a judge)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (Dem Group RET, Nat. Assn School, Psychologist, NYC,1972 March 14; RET Dem Nat. Assn School psychologists, 1972 March 14)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (Albert Mol, interview, Holland and US; Synore Trisri-Grad. Student st SUNY Stony Brook)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (RET group dem-carleton univ. ottowa, Albert Ellis, 1973 April 8)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (RET Workshop, #4, 1971 September 19; cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (RET for School Psychologists, Cleveland, 1973 April 21; RET Dem)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (Cleveland Workshop, 1973 May; Cleveland)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (RET Dem-Diane Paszkowski, Duquene Univ, Ellis,1973 January 20; RET Dem, 1973 January 20)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (RET Workshop Dem, 1973 April 24; cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (American Ontoanalytic Assoc., Albert Ellis, Mon May 10, Psychotherapy and value of a human being; Albert Ellis, Mon. May 11, AOA, Psychotherapy)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (desirability of workg evn when depresd-1972 March; ROMDA, nd to be king, 1974 February)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (ODOED, Prog. w/shithood, 1972 June)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (Mich. Soc. Workers Assoc. Workshop, RET, Ellis interview with young mother, 1971 May 8; interview w/young husband)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (IEFPA, depresd, suicidal, 1973 April)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (NAMED, lk of orgasm, 1974 ALGAN, prog. w/wife and drinkg, 1974)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (TLAES, anx abt sex, 1972 October; LAHRA)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (ROMRI, fr of pub spkg, 1972 August; FEHMA, numb abt numbness, 1974 February)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (MIZHE, prog w/independence, 1974 March; interview w/editors of penguin books)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (IPSRD, behvr ther and RET, 1972 June)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (RET and Drug Abuse, Solon, Ohio, 1974 May; RET Dem Solon Drug Abuse Center, Ohio, 1974 May, young male afraid to assert self w/wife)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (RET Workshop, Seattle, 1974 April)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (RET group Dem-female afraid to approach new males, 1974 May)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (RTSRD, reality ther, 1974 NEVEI, wrk insecurity, 1974 March)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (RET Workshop, Battle Creek, 1974 May)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (RET Dems, London, 1974 July; RET Dem, Houston, woman W D who goofs on house work, 1974 July)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (RET Workshop, Toronto, 1974 June; RET Dem, Irv. Angry at wife, Toronto, 1974 June)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (RET Talk-Riveredge Hosp., Chicago, 1974 May; RET Dems, Riveredge Hosp., Chicago, 1974 May)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (RET Dem with a coule, Houston, 1974 March; RET Dem, jealous female, Houston, 1974 March)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (RET Workshop, athens, Ohio, Ellis, 1974 May 18; RET and Treatment of Adolescents, 1974 May 17 on TV)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (RET Workshop, Battle Creek, Indl Dem; cont Group Therapy)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (Clearwater Workshop, 1974 April; cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (RET Workshop, Phila, 1974 May 19; How to be an Unashamed hedonist unprofane, 1974 May)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (Albert Ellis, visit with Mrs. Hettie Ellis and Janet Greer, 1973 September 23; Interview with Jim Stingley, L.A. Times, RET, 1973 September 23)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (RET Dem, Iowa City, 1973 Interview on Privacy on marriage with Laurie Lyle,1973 October 30)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (LDGRD, how to accept self,1974 January; Interv. w/Geoffrey Muirden,1974 January)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (Group Dem. Clearwater,1972 August; Interview w/Donald Meichenbaum, 1974 January)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (ROHSE, 13 yr old boy w/Anx abt going to H.S.; Interview with Walter Block and Dick Bullock (continued),1974 January 7)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (IRPLA, certainty Nd, 1973 November; Interview w/ W/Block and D. Bullock,1974 January 7)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 23)
      (AHSDE, 1972 September 11, deprsd-shd be better fast-nd to be outstndg-tripped,1972 September 21;1972 September 18 deciding wht she wnts to do and nt what others want//puttg self down fr turng onto a druggied,1972 October 2)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Albert Ellis and Maxie Maultsby,1971 June 30; Group Supervision, Albert Ellis, 1971)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Interview: Jason Aronson; Interview: Frank Adducci-Psychology of Adolescents,1973 July 19)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Interview with Niel Everest on the sensuous Person,1973 June 17; Interview with Ed Brown and Donna on RET)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (CUSAR, prog, Inter: Sex ther,1973 July)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Interview on RET,1973 February 12, Phoenix; cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Interview: George Breen,1973 June 12; David Leiter, Interview on Studying Social Work)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (NAKDE, Albert Ellis, obsessed with lesbian ideas-worthless,1971 January 23; NAKDE,1971 January 26)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Londons Sun, Richard the strange-sensuous person,1973 May 12; Interviews, Dennis Doden, Group Sex, 1973 March 8)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (ODOED, depresd at W's leaving, 1972 May; prog. w/females, 1972 June )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Interview with Father Malachi, Meredith Found; cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (ELRGE, scared of nty ,1973 July 31;AHCDA, lateness to apptment and prog w toothbrushing ,1973 August 2)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Interviews, Sol Gordon, Sex and Energy-Mary Ann Raynes, 1973 January )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (IPSRI, intense jlsy of wfs hvg sex w/other men-down self,1974 February 26;NOBSI, puttg self down-giving up easily on wtv, 1973)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Workshop on RET, Intro Talk and tape recording and discussion, Dubuque, IA,1971 June 19; cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (RET Workshop Group Dem, Pensacola,1973 June)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (ROHAR, hypnosis,1974 March, poor tape mech)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Sex Guilt and Frustration,1973 October; How to Really be your own best friend,1973 October)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (RET, Norman, older male who hates himself for being influenced, Musnegon, Mich,1973 November 5; Talk: Case for sexual liberty, Lehigh Community College, Albert Ellis,1973 November 7)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (RET and Sex and Love Problems,1974 February 16; RET dem Mediation Fellowship, ROVRI,1974 February 16)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Cognitive Behavior Therapy, Davenport, Iowa,1972 March 12; RET Dem, 30 yr. old woman who is procrastinating, 1972 March 14)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Ohio Rehabiliation Assn., Annual Mtg. Workshop, Rat. Psych. And Counseling for Handicapped Individuals,1971 September 16)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Davenport, Iowa, Talk to Soc. Workers with child clients; Davenport, Iowa, Talk to Teachers of Disturbed Children, 1973)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (How to Conquer Weekend Lonliness; RET and Group Espousal, 1973 November)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Albert Ellis, Are we Undergoing a sex revolution?, 1969 January 12; Sex problems of college students, Univ. Delaware,1970 October 9)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (GOKJE, nd fr success with girls-shithead, 1973 LOGAL, whing abt WF's int in other men, 1973 September 11)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (RET Dems, 15 yr old boy, Scottsdale Guidance Center, Arizona, 1973 February 11; RET Dems cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (RET Dem, Austin, Mary angry at me, 1974 July; RET Dem, San Antonio, 1974 July)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (RET Dem, Donia unable to write poetry anx abt anx, Toronto, 1974 June; Toronto Workshop cont,1974 June)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (RET Dem, young man w/prob w/WP, Irvine, CA, 1973 September; RET Dem, Irvine, CA, 1973 September low recordings)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (RET Dems, 1972)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (APGA, film with Joan, Atlanta,1973 May 28; Atlanta, RET Dem, 1973 May 28)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (NYC Attendance, Teachers Workshop,1971 January 27; cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (RET Workshop, Palo Alto, 1973 February 10; RET Dems)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (RET Workshop, Atlanta, 1973 May; cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Therapists Group, 1974 January 2)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Therapists Group, 1974 January 16, Mike, prob w/thesis; cont, Pat-getting doctorate-Liane-divorcg H)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Therapists Group, 1973 December 19; cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (GAWPE,1973 March 16, intent to change behvr when he is home)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (GAWPE,1973 March 8; RAHRI, 1973 August 6, unusual prog-overcoming boredom)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (1973 May 15)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (BRUKE,1972 May 30, anx state-phobia abt aprching girl; IRPLA, acceptg self and B F-hostility and self-downg,1972 October 5)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Therapists Group,1974 May 8)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (HSOMI, 1972 November 15, alc-self dmng frATc; ERFAR,1973 October 1 )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (ETSER,1973 September 27, cnt urinate in public-impotent w/females; IEGDE, nd to direct play perfectly, 1973)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (GAWPE, steals; 1973 February 27, upset abt not spkg rapidly enough in group)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (FIGHO,1972 April 7, indecisive-depresd-condemng self;1972 April 20, prog w/hvg sex and givg upon recalcitrant BF)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (GAWPE, stealg bks of nd fr lv and hostility to M and her lver; 1973 March 1, upset abt B's cmt lcism and M's upset)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (GAWPE, 1973 March 6, real prog w awfulizg and frust; GAWPE, 1973 March 12, real prog w homework report)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (RET, Wesleyan Univ.,1971 March 17; Sex without Guilt, 1971 March 17)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Rationality and Irrationality in the group process, Adelphi Univ.,1971 June 20; IASRP Group Supervision,1971 September 15)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (NYC Attendance Teachers, 1971 January 28; cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (RET Workshop, Western Ill. Univ. Macomb, 1974 February 2; cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (IOPRU, 1973 July, blamg self and not listng to ther; NIWBA, 1973 July, fr of losg job)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Atlantic Community College Workshop in RE Psychotherapy, 1971 May 23; cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Pensacola Workshop, Talk on RET, 1973 June 29; questions)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (RET Dem, Columbua, 1974 February; RET Dem Columbus, 1974 February 24)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (RET Dem,Henderson Clinic, Ft Lauderdale-Dave, 1974 February; RET Workshop, 1974 February)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (RET Dems, Marilyn-Cleveland, 1974 February; RET Dem, John blushg)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (Western Ill Univ., 1973 February 1, RET Dem-yng male afrd to tlk to females; cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (KAWST, 09/1974; Rosemary Wittman-Passion)
      (Note in case: KAWST, 1973 September, Injustice--Interesting message, as Al remembered his adventures in taxi-riding, airplane schedules and had shoulders. But, the pt. doesn’t do much except listen, although he does he does seem to "get" the RET message at the end. No identifying names are used. High intensity hum mars and otherwise acceptable sound recording. Not a good example of therapy because the point is so passive. Ric )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (RET Dem, 1973 April 7, Ottawa-35 yr old angry with mother; Ottawa, 1973 April 7, RET Dem-detached young female)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 24)
      (RET Dem, Cleveland, Marilyn, 1974 February 9, Sherryl Dem)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (RUBKA,1973 August 23, real prog w drinkg-F's disturb; AHCDA, 1973 August 16, blamng self fr complsns and inadeqcies)
      (Note in case: Review of side with F. Sound quality-good. Much of the tape does not exemplify RET methodology. A fair amount of time is spent by the client relating history. Not good for publication.)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (RET workshop, Germany, 1971 July 21; cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (RTSDA; EFPDO, 1973 February--D writing block-difficult client)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (RIFRI, He sexly bored, she compulsv; RIFCA, How not to get angry,1972 May)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (Therapists group-1974 June 5-Steve-Helping clients; Joel-angry and hurt abt wife's not seeing his nobility)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (Therapists Group, 1972 April 4)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (Group Supervision, 1971 July 28; cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (LAPNA,1973 October 1--tape ends after 20 minutes, Shame-Nd for T's love-upset abt his criticism; DORLO, 1972 June 15, lk of confidence-anger-prog durg sessn)
      (Note in case:LAPNA, 1973 October 6. There are 2 sessions on this side of the tape totalling only 30 minutes. Although there are valuable aspects to both sessions I would not recommend either because of their incompleteness. J Block)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (Therapists Group, 1972 November 19)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (Therapists Group, 1972 October 18)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (Fellowship Group Therapy, 1973 October 3; cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (ROMDA,1973 May 14, Practicg helpg self and downg self fr goofg; RUBKA, 1973 August 9, dealg w shame avoidance at wrk)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (RAHJE, 1973 June 2, two psychotic -musts and perfectionism; WOHME, 1973 June 17, not disputg self downg ideas)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (AHCDA,1973 August, contamination and washg after toilet touchg; GALRD, real prog by 11 yr. old boy-self-acceptnce and vulnerability)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (DUGLY, demndg she be betr lkg and mr competent; 1972 September 25, worthlessns-admitg-wrkg agnst it)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (KEPGE,1973 September, dep and glty; OOMSH, 1973 September, prog in not upsetg self)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (CEBMA, 1973 October, acceptg lv affr w boss in spite of its limitation [adult]; BURJE, paranoia abt W May be carg fr another man)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (RAMKE, hatg W fr controlg him, 1972 December 19; 1973 January 26, demndg tht W and others treat him well)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (KAWST,1973 July 31, Lv nd and demndg he do the right thing-philosophic discussion; AHCDA, 1973 August 1, Sm prog W toothbrushg compulsion)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (GTSRA,1973 August 20, Disputg his ideas leadg to complsns; ARFSA, 1972 April 18, Glty abt relatg to W and other women too dply)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (Supervision-Psychotics and Their Treatment,1973 October 24; WOLUD, How to make sex more exciting, 1973 October 20)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (DELEV,1972 April 18, Blamg self fr D's flore; LABSH,1973 October, Psychosis and Paranoid)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (RACMD and RACBA, She d herself abot his decision to divorce; He resolved to separate and wrk on his glt self-defama)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (AHSDE, Boxg self in w blamg, 1972 October 4;1972 October 25, puttg self down)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (Therapists Group, 1974 April 10, Ron's anger; Ross's upset abt D son-in-law)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (DCMLI, 1972, cryg and ashmd of cryg-shithood-fr of rejectn, OK for written transcript; LIWFR,1973 October 16, fightg shithood)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (EHSJE, 1973 prog in acceptg H gettg him to do better; RAMRA, 1973 October 17, not damng people for their acts)
      (Note in case: EHSJE, 1973 2nd session, sound quality is good. RET methodology is good. This patient aspires to run for congress given the remote possibility that she does and is successful plus the current predudice against political candidates having seen a shrink. tape May be a problem-although on the other hand there are no concrete identifiable statements. Pateint talks sufficiently and is getting the RET message. Recommended with the qualification noted above. RAMRA,1973 October 17, Sound quality good, although there is a brief break at the beginning. RET methodology good. No identifiable material. Client talks sufficiently but seems to be "yessing" Albert more than accepting and understanding the RET message. Not recommended. signed J. Block)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (Therapists Group,1974 April 24, shame exercises)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (Therapists Group,1974 July 3, Pat-Michael; Steve)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (Therapists Group,1972 November 1)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (Therapists Group,1974 March 21, Steve and Michael; cont)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (LEBCA,1972 March 24, Blames self fr nt being assertv w males; anx-1972 April 14, shyness-acceptg new role at wrk;1972 March31, self-reinforcement schedules-ndg lv and depressn)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (RET Dem: Sychophantic client, 1973 Thurs. Group, 6:30, 1974 September 9, Joe-Marv, Tyler, Tom)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (NOJHA and NOJAU,1972 December 14, She is disgustd w sex-lk of comunica-she glty and self-downg; She ct hv romantic attachment and lv her H too)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (UAVTE,1973 January 27, sm prog w self-downg-cnt lk pepl; GTSRA, 1973 August 11, rituals and compulsions)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (SELNE, Heroin addiction-self-blmg-low frust tolerance; 1973 February 22 determind to stay off heroin)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (RAMKE,1972 November 6, fr of flg at schl and anx abt anx; RAHAU, 1973 December 12, fr of gtg job and mmg social contrls)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (NAMAL, boredom lk of purpose, 1973 RACJA, cog. Desensitization,1974 February)
      (Note in case: RAHAU, Undated. Found good. Methodology-very forceful. Might have been at least a little warmer. Mention of first names only. Client speaks sufficiently but is not particularly responsive. Not recommended. Reviewer-J. Block)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (SAMJO, Sm. Prog. W anger,1973 November, KAWST, 1973 April, rebellg agnst boss; Ft Lauderdale Workshop,1973 December 16)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (LIWJA, 1974 Anger and Anx; TANTR, 1974 September, Fr of exams-lack of confidence)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (LOGAL, obsesd w WF,1973 October; ROHSE, refusg to wrk at schl,1973 November)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (AMSLO, compromising w H on swinging; Angry at H, 1972)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (BULJA, appropriate and inappropriate emotions,1972 June 18-anger;1972 June 7, perfectionism abt W--1972 June 10, tolerance)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (AHCDA,1973 November 1, how humans mk up arbitrary rules)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (NETVE and NETSU, 1973 equ and workg hard-She putg self down in past; RET Dem. Young male with sexy but inad. Woman friend. St Petersburg, 1973 October)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (ROHAR, poor erection,1973 August 17; AHCDA,1973 August 15, working on complsns)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (BARSH, low frustr tolerance in gettg job and W bfs, not good for public presentation; AHCDA, 1973 October 1, sm. Prog in getg to therapy on time)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (CEBIR, dfculty of humans chng, 1972 August ;1972 September, low frust tolerance)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (SEWSA, 1973 June 12, Real prog. W self and BF; RABNA, 1973 June 16, presn-cnt tk pot)
      (Note in case: SEWSA, patient is a woman who sounds as though she was probably quite rational to begin with; thus is not a typical patient. 1973 December. Signed JLW)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (LOGRO,1972 March, fr of going crazy, self-downg)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (LOGRE, 1972 April, fr of going crazy. Sm prog., 4-track)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (AHSAR,1973 May 31, acceptg injustices of the world; Barbara Howell, Cosmo-How to handle selfish man)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (WOLJO, 1972 November 23, nd to put everyone but himself in one category; RET Workshop, St. Petersburg, 1973 October 27)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (ELRGE,1973 August, fear of marrg WF; LOGAL, Image of self, 1973 August)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (LEPMA, 1972 April, blamg self; NEBPA, blmg self, 1972)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (MASST, 1974 July 17, musts-anx-lft; Interview on wealthy clients with Jackie Thompson, 1974 April 22)
      (Note in case: MASST,1974 July, Sound-good. Methodology good. No identifiable info. Referral source might be blipped out. Client is mostly acquiescing, he is superficially responsive. Not recommended. Signed J. Block)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 25)
      (RTSDA,1973 June, Relates to women mainly sxly-lk of confidence; RAWST,1973 January 17, worth and rejection-Indl is worthless and has no value in his existence)